Continuing Education Pamphlet Collection
Continuing Education Pamphlet Collection
various
University of the State of New York
90 linear ft. (approx.)
Pamphlets, journals, directories, newsletters, etc related to adult and continuing education, from the United States as well as from countries from Finland to Thailand
2458669
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Continuing Education Pamphlet Collection is a truly comprehensive selection of adult and continuing education related publications from around the world. Organizations represented include the Adult Education Association of the Unites States (AEA/USA), the Council on the Continuing Education Unit (CCEU), the Center for the Study of Liberal Ed. for Adults (CSLEA), EDUCAFRICA, the European Centre for Development of Vocational Training, International Council on Adult Education (ICAE), L'ICEA, UNESCO, and the Worker's Education Association (WEA). Countries represented range from Argentina to Japan to Zimbabwe. The content includes pamphlets, journals, periodicals, directories, newsletters, monographs, and more.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection itself is not arranged in any particular order. The finding aid is arranged alphabetically, with cross-references; every attempt has been made to note and reference related material, but the researcher would be wise to check under variant names of people and/or organizations as well as under their acronyms to ensure finding all relevant material.
A box listing, without cross-references, is also provided at the end of this finding aid.
Related Material
The library holds a considerable number of collections related to adult and continuing education. Please refer to for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Adult education; Adult education; Continuing education; Directories.; Newsletters.; Journals (periodicals); Pamphlets.; Reports.; Educators.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the U.S. Department of Education; University of the State of New York; Roger Hiemstra.
Inventory
- Alphabetical listing
  - AAAE (American Association for Adult Education) (Box 14)
  - AAAE Adult Education News (Box 40)
  - AC, ACE (Box 2)
  - AC/UNC Newsletter (Box 3)
  - Academy News (Box 40)
  - Accreditation (Box 40)
  - Accreditation-CEU (Box 45)
    See also Council on the Continuing Education Unit (CCEU)
  - Acquisition lists
    - Georgia Center Continued Education (Box 66)
    - NUFFIC-CESO (Box 67)
    - Open University (Box 66)
    - University of Reading (Box 67)
    - University of Liverpool (Box 66)
  - Activity (Box 40)
  - Activity (ACT) (Box 22)
  - The AC-UNU (Box 22)
  - AC-UNU Newsletter (Box 40)
  - Administration (Box 51)
    See also Adult Education Administration
  - Administration (Box 48)
  - Administration Principles (Box 49)
  - Administration Superintendents (Box 51)
  - Adult Agencies: International (Box 49)
  - Adult and Continuing Education Today (Box 40)
  - Adult Basic Education (ABE)
    - Adult Basic Education (ABE) (Box 45)
    - Adult Basic Education (ABE) (Box 53)
    - The Adult Basic Education (ABE) Curriculum and Its Development (Box 30)
    - in Mississippi (Box 56)
    - National Teacher Training Study (Box 4)
    - Pamphlets and Publications, Misc. (Box 75)
    - Pamphlets and Publications, Misc. (Box 76)
    - Pamphlets and Publications, Misc. (Box 77)
    - Pamphlets and Publications, Misc. (Box 78)
    - Research Center (Box 75)
    - Staff and Conference (Box 4)
  - Adult Correctional Education (Box 61)
    See also Adult Literacy Responses to Comic Strip Narratives Among Inmates of a Correctional Institution
  - Adult Education, A Journal of Research and Theory, 1960-1982; 1956,; 1957 (Box 10)
  - Adult Education Administration (Box 46)
    See also Administration
  - Adult Education Association (AEA) Leadership Pamphlets (Box 4)
  - Adult Education Association (AEA) Leadership Digest (Box 4)
  - Adult Education Association of the U.S. (AEA/USA) (Box 49)
  - Adult Education Clearinghouse (Box 40)
  - Adult Education Monograph, "Civil Defense for Adult..." (Box 2)
  - Adult Education Newsletter (Box 40)
  - Adult Education Professional Teachers (Box 65)
  - Adult Education Students (Box 65)
  - Adult Education Teachers (Box 66)
  - Adult Education Teaching (Box 65)
  - Adult Education-U.S. Agencies (Box 49)
  - Adult Education and Development (Box 9)
  - The Adult Educator (Box 22)
  - Adult Finances (Box 49)
  - Adult Leadership (Box 22)
  - Adult Literacy and Basic Skills Unit (Box 40)
  - Adult Literacy Responses to Comic Strip Narratives Among Inmates of a Correctional Institution (Box 61)
    See also Adult Correctional Education
  - Adult Organizations (Box 52)
  - Adult Programs on Aging (Box 56)
  - Adult Student Personnal Association (ASPA), See A Decade for Development (ASPA)
  - The Adult View (Box 22)
  - AEC - U.S. National Association Institution (Box 60)
  - AEC Berkeley/Santa Barbara (Box 59)
  - AEC UNESCO (Box 60)
    See also UNESCO
  - AES Journal on Postsecondary Education (Box 41)
  - Affinities (Box 22)
  - Africa (Box 5)
    See also Continuing Education in Africa; EDUCAFRICA; Journal of the African Association for Literature; Kenya; Nigeria; South Africa; West Africa Crier-Newsletter of the Subregion: AALAE
  - Agencies, Misc. (Box 31)
  - Agencies, Organizations, and Sponsors Civic Literacy (Box 46)
  - Agencies: Non-Governmental (Box 49)
    See also Non-Governmental Universities and Colleges
  - Agency for Instructional Television Newsletter (Box 41)
  - Age and aging, See Adult Programs on Aging; Aging News; Aging Programs; Education for Aging; Education for Aging News; Education for Senior Adults; Gerontology: Older Adult Learner; News Education for Aging; Programs on Aging
  - Aging News (Box 22)
  - Aging Programs (Box 69)
  - Agricultural Education (Box 56)
  - Agricultural News (Box 22)
  - AICS Compass (Box 41)
  - Aid Highlight (Box 41)
  - Aker, George (Box 14)
  - ALBSU (Box 22)
  - Alfalit (Box 41)
  - ALL (Box 22)
  - American Foundation for Continuing Education, Case Stories in American Politics (Box 4)
  - American Medical Asociation (Box 22)
  - American Medical Association (AMA) Continuing Medical Education Fact Sheet (Box 41)
    See also Continuing Medical Education Newsletter
  - AMT Events (Box 16)
  - AMT Events (Box 22)
  - AONTAS (Ireland) (Box 5)
    See also Ireland
  - Arbeits-und Sozialrecht be Luchterhand (Box 16)
  - Argentina (Box 32)
  - Aries (Box 2)
  - Asian South Pacific Bureau of A.E. (Box 22)
  - ASPBAE Courier (Box 16)
  - Association for Continuing Higher Education (ACHE) (Box 14)
    See also Five Minutes with ACHE
  - Association for Continuing Higher Education (ACHE) (Box 48)
  - Association for World Education Newsletter (Box 16)
  - Association of Teacher Education (Box 22)
  - Association of University Evening Colleges (AUEC) (Box 18)
  - Association of University Evening Colleges (AUEC) (Box 30)
  - ASTD Educational Programs (Box 71)
  - ATE Newsletter (Box 16)
  - Australia (Box 5)
  - Australia (Box 32)
  - Australia (Box 33)
  - Australian Journal of Adult Education (Box 16)
  - Austria (Box 32)
  - Availability/Accessibility of Support Services (Box 32)
  - Bangladesh (Box 5)
  - Bank Street News (Box 16)
  - Basic Choices (Box 16)
  - Basic Education (Box 53)
  - BBC Continuing Education Newsletter (Box 16)
  - BCEL (Box 22)
  - BCEL (Box 3)
  - Benchmark (Box 16)
  - Benchmark (Box 22)
  - Bibliography of Publishers (Box 30)
  - Bibliography [unspecified] (Box 30)
  - Bibliography [unspecified] (Box 30)
  - Bibliography [unspecified] (Box 46)
  - Bilingual and Bicultural Programs (Box 56)
  - Boeck, Alvord (Box 30)
  - Botswana (Box 32)
  - Brazil (Box 33)
  - Brenton Stevenson, University of Toledo (Box 30)
  - British Columbia (Box 5)
  - British Open University Foundation (Box 16)
  - Bulletin of Continuing Education in International Affairs (Box 22)
  - Business Council Effective Literacy (Box 22)
  - CAEL (Box 21)
  - CAETA (Box 21)
  - Campus Market Report (Box 21)
  - Canada (Box 33-36)
    See also Canadian Adult Education; Canadian Journal of University Continuing Education; Continuing Education in Canada; Statements on Adult Education by Council of Europe, Germany, and Canada; Worldlit Newsletter of World Literacy of Canada
  - Canadian Adult Education (Box 18)
  - Canadian Journal of University Continuing Education (Box 16)
  - Capsule Report (Box 21)
  - Capsules (Box 16)
  - Captrends (Box 16)
  - Career Training (Box 21)
  - Caribbean (Box 5)
  - Caribbean Regional Council for Adult Education (Box 39)
  - Carnegie Quarterly (Box 16)
  - Carnegie Quarterly (Box 21)
  - CASAE/ACEEA Newsletter (Box 16)
  - Catalyst (Box 16)
  - CAUCE Bulletin (Box 16)
  - CCEU, See Council on the Continuing Education Unit (CCEU)
  - CEC News (Box 21)
  - CEDEFOP (Box 21)
  - CEDEFOP News (Box 16)
  - CEDEFOP Vocational Training Bulletin (Box 16)
  - Center for Adult Learning and Education Credentials (Box 21)
  - Center for Continuing Education of Women (Box 16)
  - Center for Ecomomic and Social Information (Box 21)
  - Center for the Study of Liberal Education for Adults (CSLEA) (Box 18)
  - Center for the Study of Liberal Education for Adults (CSLEA) - Sandy (Box 30)
  - Centergram (Box 16)
  - CERES (Box 21)
  - CESO (Box 16)
  - CESO (Box 3)
  - Charitable Foundations (Box 50)
  - Charters, Alexander N. (Box 21)
  - Child Care Programs (Box 56)
  - Chile (Box 36)
  - China (Box 5)
  - China (Box 36)
  - Choices (Box 7)
  - Christians and Israel (Box 3)
  - Clearinghouse Adell (Box 52)
  - Coalition of Adult Education Organizations (CAEO) (Box 18)
  - Coalition of Adult Education Organizations (CAEO) (Box 21)
  - Coast Communicator (Box 21)
  - Cochran, Harry A. (Box 30)
  - COE New trends (Box 41)
  - COE Newsletter (Box 41)
  - Collage (Box 21)
  - College of Agricultural and Life Sciences Quarterly (Box 4)
  - College of Agricultural Life Science (Box 21)
  - COMBASE (Box 3)
  - COMBASE: Newsletter/Community-based programs that work (Box 41)
  - Commission of Professors of Adult Education (CPAE) Newsletter (Box 1)
    See also Professors for Adult Education
  - Commission of Professors of Adult Education (CPAE) of AEA of USA Newsletter (Box 41)
  - Commisssion on Higher Education (Box 21)
  - Commissions on Higher Education; "Letter" (Box 3)
  - Commonwealth (Box 39)
  - Commonwealth News (Box 41)
  - Communication (Box 51)
  - Community Agencies (Box 50)
  - Community Colleges for International Development-International News (Box 41)
  - Community Colleges; Misc. info (Box 1)
  - Community Development (Box 2)
  - Community Education (Box 46)
  - Community Education (Box 46)
  - Community Education (Box 57)
  - Community Education Journal (Box 21)
  - Community Education Journal (Box 41)
  - Community Education Today (Box 41)
  - Community Services; CATALYST (Box 41)
  - Comparative Adult Education Newsletter (Box 41)
  - Comparative Education of Latin America: Costa Rica (Box 76)
  - Comparative Education Review (Box 7)
  - Comparative and International Education Society (CIES) (Box 40)
  - Comparative and International Education Society (CIES) (Box 21)
  - COMPAS (Box 21)
  - Competency (Box 28)
  - Competency Based Adult Education (CBAE) (Box 46)
  - Competency Based Adult Education (CBAE) Futures (Box 46)
  - Conferences
    See also Adult Basic Education (ABE) Staff and Conference; Conference on ICUAE; ICUAE Conference 1976; Lifelong Learning Research Conference Proceedings; Michigan State University Conferences: 1961, 67, 69, 76
    - 30th All India Adult Education Conference (Box 59)
    - Adult Education Conference (Box 4)
    - Adult Education Conference of North America, etc. (Box 59)
    - Adult Education Research Conference (AERC) (Box 14)
    - Adult Education International Aid and Poverty Conference (Box 58)
    - Conference on Education and Occupational Needs of Asian-Pacific-American Women: National Institution of Education (Box 60)
    - Conferences on Adult Education (Box 57)
    - Conferences, meetings, and symposiums (Box 45)
    - Conference-U.S. National Association Institution (Box 70)
    - First International Conference on Comparative Adult Ed (Box 59)
    - Fourth International Conference on Adult Education (Box 67)
    - International Conferences (Box 57)
    - Research Conference (Box 58)
    - U.S. National Groups Conferences (Box 60)
  - CONNECT (Box 21)
  - Consumer Education (Box 60)
  - Contact with Denmark (Box 21)
    See also Denmark
  - Continuing Edition (Box 21)
  - Continuing Education in Africa (Box 4)
  - Continuing Education in Canada (Box 3)
  - Continuing Education (Box 41)
  - Continuing Educator (SACEM) (Box 41)
    See also Society for the Advancement of Continuing Education for Ministry (SACEM)
  - The Continuing Educator (Box 1)
  - Continuing Medical Education Newsletter (Box 41)
    See also American Medical Association (AMA) Continuing Medical Ed. Fact Sheet
  - Convergence (Box 8)
  - Converging Trends (Box 41)
  - Cooperation South (Box 7)
  - Cooperative Extension (Box 60)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension (Box 4)
  - Cornell International Agriculture Monograph (Box 41)
  - Cornerstone (Box 21)
  - Costa Rica, See Comparative Education of Latin America: Costa Rica
  - Council of Europe (Box 67)
  - Council on the Continuing Education Unit (CCEU) (Box 21)
    See also Accreditation-CEU
  - Council on the Continuing Education Unit - CCEU Reporter (Box 16)
  - Council on the Continuing Education Unit - CCEU Reporter (Box 1)
  - Councilgram (Box 21)
  - Counseling (Box 46)
  - Counseling (Box 62)
  - Course trends in Adult Learning (Box 21)
  - CRESST (Box 3)
  - CRESST Evaluation Comment (Box 41)
  - CSE Evaluation Comment (Box 41)
  - Czechoslovakia (Box 36)
  - D.K. Agencies (Box 19)
  - DAE Newsletter (Box 42)
  - Data Base Systems (Box 31)
  - A Decade for Development (ASPA) (Box 30)
  - Decade Watch (Box 3)
  - Denmark (Box 36)
    See also Contact with Denmark
  - Development Communication Report (Box 42)
  - Directories
    See also Resources, print: misc. directories
    - Adult Education at Syracuse University directories, misc. (Box 29)
    - Council of Europe: Education Directories (Box 40)
    - Directories on Adult Education Resources, Misc. (Box 63)
    - Directories on Adult Education Resources, Misc. (Box 64)
    - Directories on Adult Education Resources, Misc. (Box 65)
    - Guides, Directories, Resources (Box 2)
    - International, misc. directories, 1980's (Box 53)
    - Professional resumes: misc. directories (Box 31)
  - Dissertation correspondence (Box 30)
  - Dissertations, Master Theses (Box 2)
  - Draper Fund Report (Box 19)
  - Dropouts (Box 50)
  - Dyer, John (Box 30)
  - Earth Watch (Box 19)
  - Economics Education (Box 68)
  - EDUCAFRICA (Box 42)
  - Education Adult Evaluation (Box 50)
  - Education Adult Instruction Methods (Box 49)
  - Education for Aging (Box 19)
  - Education for Aging News (Box 42)
  - Education in Europe (Box 18)
  - Education Exchange (Box 19)
  - Education Journalism (Box 39)
  - Education Policy Fellowship Program (Box 6)
  - The Education Quarterly (Box 26)
  - Education Record (Box 42)
  - Education for Senior Adults (Box 30)
  - Education Testing Service (Box 49)
  - Education for Tomorrow's Environment (Box 42)
  - Education and Training Programmes for Info Personnel (Box 19)
  - Education, Adult Higher: Misc. Pamphlets (Box 54-55)
  - Education, Higher Finance (Box 31)
  - The Educational Characteristics of the American People (Box 65)
  - Educational Innovation (Box 19)
  - Educational News (Box 19)
  - Educational Programs for Youth (Box 71)
  - Educational Record (Box 19)
  - Egypt (Box 36)
  - Elementary Education (Box 51)
  - Ellis, A. Caswell (Box 30)
  - En Toutes Lettres (Box 19)
  - Engineering Industry Training Board Information Paper (Box 42)
  - Engineering Training Today (Box 42)
  - England (Box 5)
  - English as a Second Language (Box 61)
  - Environment-Bibliography-Adult Education Projects (Box 32)
  - Environmental, Agricultural Education (Box 39)
  - ERIC (Box 11)
  - ERIC (Box 52)
  - ERIC on Research (Box 72)
  - Estonia (Box 36)
  - Ethiopia (Box 36)
  - Europe (Box 5)
  - European Bureau for Development of Vocational Training (Box 40)
    See also European Centre for Development of Vocational Training
  - European Bureau of Adult Education: Education Legislation (Box 40)
  - European Bureau of Adult Education: Newsletter (Box 42)
  - European Centre for Development of Vocational Training (Box 39)
  - European Centre for Development of Vocational Training (Box 76)
    See also European Bureau for Development of Vocational Training
  - European Community (Box 40)
  - Evaluation of Support Services: UNISIST (Box 32)
  - Evaluation (Box 46)
  - Exceptional Children, Education of: "The Open University" (Box 39)
  - Extension Education (Box 60)
  - Facilities (Box 52)
  - FACS (Box 19)
  - Faits Noureaux (Box 19)
  - Family Education (Box 61)
  - Family Education (Box 62)
  - Father Wirtenberger (Box 30)
  - Federal Agencies (Box 48)
  - Films of the United Nations Family (Box 30)
  - Finances (Box 46)
  - Finances (Box 52)
  - Finances: Budgets, Grants and Funding Foundations (Box 46)
  - Finland (Box 36)
  - Finland, Adult Education in (Box 2)
  - Finnish Adult Education Organizations (Box 42)
  - Five Minutes with ACHE (Box 42)
    See also Association for Continuing Higher Education (ACHE)
  - FNV (Box 19)
  - FNV News (Box 1)
  - Focus Bulletin (Box 42)
  - For the Record (Box 19)
  - For the Record (Box 42)
  - The Ford Foundation (Box 19)
  - Ford Foundation Letter (Box 42)
  - Formative Years 1940-1950 (Box 30)
  - Forumarbeit (Box 19)
  - France (Box 5)
  - France (Box 36)
  - The Free Press (Box 3)
  - Freld Research Letters (Box 30)
  - Froman, Lewis (Russel Sage College) (Box 30)
  - Georgia Center Continued Education Acquisition Lists (Box 66)
  - Georgia Center Quarterly (Box 19)
  - Georgia Center Quarterly (Box 42)
  - Georgia State (Box 30)
  - Georgia State College (Box 30)
  - Germany (Box 5)
  - Germany (Box 36)
    See also Statements on Adult Education by Council of Europe, Germany, and Canada
  - Gerontology: Older Adult Learner (Box 47)
  - Gewerkschaftliche Monatschefte (Box 9)
  - Gewerkschaftliche Monatschefte (Box 17)
  - Ghana (Box 36)
  - Gifted children, See Education of Exceptional Children, "The Open University"
  - Greece (Box 36)
  - Growing Edge (Box 17)
  - The Growing Edge (Box 19)
  - Guyana (Box 36)
  - Handicapped-Disadvantaged (Box 62)
  - Hardy, Leslie P. (Box 30)
  - Health Programs (Box 62)
  - Health Resource Center (Box 2)
  - Higher Adult Education Pamphlets, Misc. (Box 68)
  - Higher Education and National Affairs (Box 17)
  - Higher Education Research Report (Box 17)
  - Higher Education (Box 63)
  - Highlights (Box 19)
  - Historical Foundations of A.E. (Box 17)
  - History (Box 46)
  - History (Box 52)
  - History of Education Quarterly (Box 7)
  - Hockenberry, William R. (Box 30)
  - Holland (Box 5)
  - How to Learn (Box 28)
  - Hungary (Box 5)
  - ICAE
    - Education and Criminal Justice Programme Newsletter (Box 17)
    - ICAE News (Box 17)
    - Participatory Formation Newsletter (Box 17)
    - Voices Rising (Box 17)
    - Women's Program Newsletter (Box 17)
  - ICED Newsletter (Box 17)
  - ICUAE
    - Bulletin Publication by ICUAE (Box 22)
    - Conference on ICUAE (Box 58)
    - ICUAE Conference 1976 (Box 59)
  - Ideas and Action (Box 17)
  - Ideas and Action (Box 19)
  - Ideas for Action (Box 17)
  - IDRC Reports (Box 1)
  - IDRC Reports (Box 17)
  - IFWEA-IVA-FIAET (Box 1)
  - Illiteracy (Box 68)
  - ILO Information (Box 17)
  - ILO Publications (Box 19)
  - ILSCAE Newsletter (Box 17)
  - ILSS (Box 19)
  - IMPACT (Box 13)
  - Incentives vs. Industry (Box 16)
  - India (Box 5)
  - India (Box 36)
    See also 30th All India Adult Ed. Conference
  - Indian Education (Box 51)
  - Indian Educator (Box 17)
  - Indian Journal for A.E. (Box 17)
  - Indian Journal of A.E. (Box 17)
  - Indian Journal of A.E. (Box 6)
  - Indice de Information (Box 2)
  - Information Census (Box 45)
  - Innotech (Box 19)
  - Innotech Newsletter (Box 17)
  - Innovation (Box 19)
  - INSERVICE (Box 17)
  - Institute for Instruction Methods: Stanford University (Box 52)
  - Instruction (Box 46)
  - Instruction Materials (Box 52)
  - Instruction Methods (Box 50)
  - Instructional Television News (Box 19)
  - Intercultural Education (Box 39)
  - Interdependent (Box 17)
  - Interlit (Box 42)
  - International Adult Education (Box 32)
  - International Associates Newsletter (Box 42)
  - International Association Newsletter (Box 6)
  - International Association of Universities of the Third Age Newsletter (Box 19)
  - International Baccalaureate Office (Box 40)
  - International Bureau of Education: Awareness List (Box 42)
  - International Corporation on Adult Education (Box 28)
  - International Council (Box 59)
  - International Council for Correspondence Education (Box 4)
  - International Development Education Program, Univ. of Pittsburg (Box 1)
  - International Handbook for Resources for Education of Adults (Box 65)
  - International History of Adult Education (Box 32)
  - International Institute for the Unification of Private Law News Bulletin (Box 19)
  - International Literacy Year (Box 19)
  - International Network for Comparative... (Box 19)
  - International Organizations: ASPBAE (Box 39)
  - International Organizations: Commission of the European Communities (Box 39)
  - International Organizations: Commonwealth Secretariat (Box 39)
  - International Organizations: Council of Europe (Box 40)
  - International Symposium on Adult Education (Box 58)
  - International University Consortium (Box 19)
  - International, misc. (Box 28)
  - International, misc. (Box 6)
    See also Scandinavian countries; names of individual countries
  - International/world Education, misc. (Box 76)
  - Introductions (Box 30)
  - Iran (Box 36)
  - Iraq (Box 5)
  - Ireland (Box 36)
    See also AONTAS (Ireland)
  - Israel (Box 36)
  - Italy (Box 36)
  - Jamaica (Box 36)
  - Japan (Box 5)
  - Japan (Box 36)
    See also Look Japan
  - Jerusalem (Box 5)
  - Journal of the African Association for Literature (Box 24)
  - Journal of World Education (Box 24)
  - Journal of World Education (Box 42)
  - Kappan (Box 24)
  - Kellog (Box 15)
  - Kellogg Project, Misc. Occasional Papers (Box 29)
  - Kenya (Box 36)
  - KENYA Journal of Adult Education (Box 42)
  - Khitpen (Box 24)
  - Korea (Box 5)
  - Korea (Box 36)
  - Labor (Box 68)
  - Labor Education Libraries (Box 47)
  - Labor Education (Box 42)
  - Ladder (PLAN) (Box 24)
  - Laubach Literacy International (Box 15)
  - Leadership, See Adult Ed. Association (AEA) Leadership Pamphlets; Adult Ed. Association (AEA) Leadership Digest; Adult Leadership; Looking into (LRI) Leadership Courses
  - Learning (Box 42)
  - Learning (Box 53)
  - Learning Connection (Box 42)
  - Learning in New York (Box 4)
  - Learning in New York (Box 24)
  - Learning in New York (Box 42)
  - The Learning Society (Box 63)
  - Legislation (Box 53)
  - Libraries and Literacy Education (Box 30)
  - Libraries: U.S. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare (Box 47)
  - Library of Continuing Education at Syracuse University (Box 15)
  - L'ICEA (Box 24)
  - L'ICEA (Box 42)
  - Life Planning with Adults (Box 30)
  - Lifelong Learning
    - Lifelong Learning (Box 24)
    - Lifelong Learning (Box 67)
    - Lifelong Learning (Box 68)
    - Lifelong Learning (Box 69)
    - Lifelong Learning Forum (Box 43)
    - Lifelong Learning Research Conference Proceedings (Box 59)